const question = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is at the core of Java?",
        A: "Method",
        B: "Variable",
        C: "Class",
        D: "Object",
        Ans: "Class"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What does a class define in Java?",
        A: "Syntax",
        B: "Object",
        C: "Method",
        D: "Template",
        Ans: "Template"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the new data type created by defining a class called?",
        A: "Method",
        B: "Object",
        C: "Instance",
        D: "Variable",
        Ans: "Object"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What keyword is used to declare a class?",
        A: "public",
        B: "void",
        C: "class",
        D: "new",
        Ans: "class"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What are the variables defined within a class called?",
        A: "Local",
        B: "Global",
        C: "Static",
        D: "Instance",
        Ans: "Instance"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What contains the code within a class?",
        A: "Variables",
        B: "Methods",
        C: "Keywords",
        D: "Instances",
        Ans: "Methods"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What operator is used to access instance variables?",
        A: ":",
        B: ";",
        C: ".",
        D: ",",
        Ans: "."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What method is used as the entry point of a Java program?",
        A: "start()",
        B: "main()",
        C: "run()",
        D: "init()",
        Ans: "main()"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which keyword is used to create a new object in Java?",
        A: "create",
        B: "build",
        C: "new",
        D: "alloc",
        Ans: "new"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What do you call a physical copy of a class?",
        A: "Template",
        B: "Instance",
        C: "Method",
        D: "Variable",
        Ans: "Instance"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Which statement correctly creates an instance of the Box class?",
        A: "Box mybox = Box();",
        B: "Box mybox = new Box();",
        C: "Box mybox = new Box;",
        D: "Box mybox = Box.new();",
        Ans: "Box mybox = new Box();"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "What do you call the members of a class collectively?",
        A: "Methods",
        B: "Variables",
        C: "Instances",
        D: "Members",
        Ans: "Members"
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "What type of variables does each instance of a class contain?",
        A: "Local",
        B: "Global",
        C: "Static",
        D: "Instance",
        Ans: "Instance"
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "What is the output of the program that declares two Box objects with different dimensions?",
        A: "Volume is 3000.0",
        B: "Volume is 162.0",
        C: "Both A and B",
        D: "None",
        Ans: "Both A and B"
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "What must be done to use a variable of a class type before assigning an object to it?",
        A: "Define",
        B: "Declare",
        C: "Initialize",
        D: "Assign",
        Ans: "Declare"
    }
];

export default question;
